qwiki.com 2010-12-31

# Qwiki, Inc. - Privacy Policy, Content Policy

##  Qwiki, Inc.  
Privacy Policy 

### Overview

Qwiki, Inc. (“Qwiki” or “we”) provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our practices and policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from you.

### Information We Collect

We may collect information about you and your use of our website, and any products, software, data, content, and services offered on, from or through our website (collectively, the “Service”). We may collect personally identifiable information such as your name, email address, IP address, demographic and biographical information as well as other information that does not personally identify you. The following sections describe some of the ways in which we may collect information:

### Registration

We may provide you with the opportunity to register or subscribe with us. If you register or subscribe, you may provide information to us and we collect a wide variety of information about you. Such information may include personally identifiable information such as your name, email address, IP address, demographic and biographical information and other information.

### Log Files

Like many websites, we may automatically gather certain information about our Service traffic and store it in log files. We may also use third parties to gather such information. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

### Cookies

We may use cookies to keep track of some types of information while you are using our Service. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We may also use cookies to automatically collect information about your online activity on our Service, for example, which web pages you browsed, which links you clicked on, or which searches you conducted on our Service. If you choose to decline our cookies, you assume all responsibility for any resulting loss of functionality or access.

### Web Beacons (Clear GIFs, Pixel Tags)

We may employ and our third party partners may employ a software technology called web beacons, also referred to as clear GIFs or pixel tags, that help manage content on the Service by tracking what content is effective. Web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of users in order to further personalize our Service for our users and to collect a limited set of information about our users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We also may include web beacons in advertisements or promotional or other e-mail messages or to determine whether messages have been opened or acted upon. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

### How we use your information

In general, we may use information that we collect about you to: (i) provide, improve and customize the Service; (ii) conduct research and analysis about your activities on the Service, including your use of, or interest in, different parts of our Service, or products or services offered by third parties; (iii) provide customer support and manage your account; (iv) provide you information via e-mail, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about the Service or products or services offered by us or third parties; (v) monitor surveys, discussion boards, forums and/or chat rooms provided to you on the Service from us or a third party; (vi) verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests; (vii) develop and provide content and advertising from us or third parties customized based on your activity and/or interests; (viii) enforce this Privacy Policy, the Terms of Service and other applicable terms and conditions; (ix) manage our business; and (x) perform functions and activities as otherwise described to you at the time of collection of information.

### Correspondence

We may send you information on products, services, special deals, and promotions. We may also use your name and email address to send newsletters to you.

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our Service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.

### Customer Service

We may communicate with you in response to your inquiries and to manage your account. We may communicate with you by email or telephone.

### Profile

We may store information that we collect through cookies, log files, web beacons, and/or third party sources to create a “profile” of your preference and activities. We may tie your personally identifiable information to information in the profile, in order to improve and customize our Service and provide tailored promotions and marketing offers for you.

We may purchase marketing data from third parties and add it to our existing user database, to better target our advertising and to provide pertinent offers in which we think you would be interested. To enrich our profiles, we may tie this information to the personally identifiable information we have.

### Conditions Under Which We Share Information

### Aggregate Information (Non-Personally Identifiable)

We may share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers. We may combine non-personal information we collect with additional non-personal information collected from other sources. We also may share aggregated information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. This information does not identify individual users and may be used to develop the Service and to target content and advertising.

### Third Party Advertisers

Advertisements may be offered through our Service by our advertising partners. We may share usage, traffic and other information with our advertising partners for the purpose of targeting advertisements through the Service.

Our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on the Service, which allow them to recognize a user’s cookie when a user uses the Service and to measure advertising effectiveness. 

### Service Providers

We may share your personal information with our authorized service providers that may be associated with us to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include providing customer service, performing business and marketing analysis, supporting and improving the functionality of our Service, and providing or maintaining contests, surveys and other features offered through our Service. These service providers may have access to information about you, including personally identifiable information, that they need to perform their functions.

### Business Partners 

We may partner with third parties to offer you surveys, contests, products and services through our Service. When you participate in such surveys or contests, or purchase such products and services, you authorize us to share information about you, including personally identifiable information, with such third parties. If you have any questions or concerns regarding how such third parties use your information, please consult the applicable third party’s privacy policy. You agree that we will not responsible or liable for any loss or damage incurred in connection with our partnership with such third parties, their activities on our Service, and the sharing of your information with such third parties.

### Legal

We reserve the right to, and you acknowledge and agree that we may, disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe, in our sole discretion, that disclosure is reasonable to protect our or a third party’s rights; to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us or the Service; to assist in investigation, prosecution, prevention, or taking other action regarding illegal activity, fraud or other wrongdoing, or suspected illegal activity, fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect a user’s or a third party’s health or safety, such as when harm or violence against any person (including you) is threatened; or in connection with an actual or proposed corporate transaction, such as a merger, acquisition, consolidation, asset sale, divestiture, or insolvency proceeding involving all or part of our business or assets.

### Abuse Victims

Notwithstanding any other provision of this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Service, we reserve the right, but have no obligation, to disclose any your information, including personally identifiable information, if in our sole discretion, we suspect or have reason to suspect, that the information involves a victim of physical, psychological or other abuse, including without limitation elder abuse, child abuse, spousal abuse, neglect, or domestic violence. If we deem appropriate, in our sole discretion, that some information should be disclosed to authorities, we reserve the right to do so. Such authorities may include law enforcement agencies, child protection agencies, or court officials. You hereby acknowledge and agree that we have the right to make such disclosure in our sole discretion.

### Links to Other websites

The Service may contain links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by Qwiki. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such other websites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Service and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by us. 

### Age Restrictions

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 18, and in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, any information we may receive from users we know to be under the age of 18 will be purged from our database.

### Outside the United States

Any information we collect may be transferred to, stored and processed in servers located in the United States and other countries around the world. This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on Service from residents of the United States. If you are using our Service from outside the United States, you hereby acknowledge that your information may be transferred to, stored and processed in the United States where our servers may be located. Other countries may have more comprehensive data protection and privacy laws than those of the United States. By using the Service, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Changes in this Privacy Policy

Qwiki may, in its sole discretion, from time to time, modify or revise this Privacy Policy without notice, and you agree to be bound by such modifications or revisions. The most current version of this Privacy Policy can be viewed at our website.

© Copyright 2010 Qwiki, Inc.

Last updated: September 26, 2010

* * *

##  Qwiki, Inc.  
Content Policy 

Welcome to Qwiki, a revolutionary new search tool that enables you to discover more about a variety of topics through a unique and transformative audiovisual reference tool that we call a “Qwiki.” Our mission is to provide a new way of searching for and receiving information and content. If any user wishes to learn more about or view any content available through a Qwiki search, that user may click on the window pane containing that content (a “Link”), which Link will show the source of that content and provide the user the ability to link directly back to the source of that content, driving traffic to source websites, In this way, we provide a transformative way for you to search for and receive information which will enhance your experience and drive traffic to the websites of any content that appears in any Qwiki search.

We firmly believe that any content accessible through a Qwiki search is made available in a manner that is fair, beneficial for the underlying website or content provider, and consistent with and respectful of all rights of content owners. However, we also value our community, and do not wish to convey the benefits of the Qwiki service to those who do not wish to receive it. So, if you are an owner of content that is available in a Qwiki search result, and you would like us to remove that content from the Qwiki search result, please provide us with a written notice containing the six items listed below: 

  * A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;
  * Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed; 
  * a description of where the material that you claim is infringing is located on the Qwiki site, with enough detail that we may find it on the website (in most circumstances, we will need a URL); 
  * Information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to contact you, such as an address, telephone number, and, if available, an electronic mail; 
  * A statement that you have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and 
  * A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that you are authorized to act on behalf of the owner of a copyright.

For any such request, please contact us at: support@qwiki.com

Please keep in mind that we are providing this procedure for take-downs merely as a courtesy to the community. By making this procedure available or taking down any content upon request, we are not acknowledging in any way that Qwiki or our service or the availability of any content on our service infringes or violates any rights of any third party. We reserve the right at any time without notice to modify or cease entirely this policy by posting a revision to our website.
